I remember one day I tried to quit.
I slipped on a bit of ice,
cracked my laptop,
and I was like, "Fuck this,
man." I went and sat in the car,
called my boss, and he
was driving. He pulls over and he goes,
"Jamie, is it?" I was like, "No.
James Smith." "All right. Oh, yeah.
Well, Jamie, mate,
let me get up your score." "It's James."
"Yep, cheers.
Cool." He goes through it and he goes,
"Well, according to your data, you get one
sale every 100 doors." I went,
"Yeah." He goes,
"How many more sales do you need
for the day?" I was like,
"Two." He's like, "All right.
Well,
knock on 200 more fucking doors then." Put
the phone down.
[laughing]
I was like, "Do you know what?
Now he's put it like that." Went
and knocked on the
next door, got told to fuck off. I
was like, "199 left."
Yeah.
And my focus went more on people saying no
to them when someone went, "Do you know
what? Come in.
British Gas just put our rates up." I
was shocked.
I became so focused on getting nos from
people that when a yes came, I was like,
"Well, that's bloody pleasant." Again,
for this content creation, people
are going
to be sat there in a comfortable
environment in their house
or in their studio or
in their office.
They're going to talk down the lens of a
DSLR camera into the
black glass disc, which is kind of weird,
and if it bombs, no one's going to see
it. Whereas in a shopping center,
people pretend you're invisible.
They say, "No, thanks." On a door,
people tell you to fuck off.
People say, "Get a real job.
I thought you were here to read the
meter." The
reactions and stuff you get in real life.
Online, people just swipe past it,
or the algorithm will never even show it
to them
in the first place.
You're not losing anything by putting
yourself out there in
content.
It's not like every video you put out,
you shorten your life or
anything like that. It's just an attempt.
You will get better.
Unfortunately, you will eat shit.
But if you can just smile
and rub it off like people in jujitsu,
CEOs,
multimillionaires, you've got Tom Hardy,
then you've got a high school teacher.
When they lose, they smile,
they take the feedback, they get up,
they continue.
They don't choose to be humiliated.
They choose to be educated.